adwerx.com 2018-12-30

# Adwerx

### Adwerx Web Site Privacy Policy

Revised as of September 13, 2016 

Welcome to the website Adwerx.com (the “Site”), owned, produced and operated by Adwerx, Inc. (“Adwerx”) (together with its affiliates, successors, and assigns, hereinafter collectively referred to as “our”, “we”, “us”, or “Adwerx”). Adwerx cares about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please email us at  [privacy@adwerx.com](mailto:privacy@adwerx.com). We may change or add to this Privacy Policy from time-to-time, so we encourage you to review it periodically. 

**SCOPE**  
This Privacy Policy applies to the collection of personal information from users of this Site. It relates to information we collect from you, including personally identifying information (also referred to as “PII”) and information that does not identify you personally. PII may include, for example, some or all of the following: your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, passwords, credit/debit card information, user name and password, and demographic information. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of the Adwerx platform (“Adwerx Platform”) for delivering digital advertising, including the use of the Adwerx Platform on the Site. For information about privacy on the Adwerx Platform click here. By using this Site you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, whether or not you register as a registered user of the Site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USED BY ADWERX**  
When users register with the Site (“Registered User”), Adwerx collects personal information submitted by the Registered User such as name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number. Adwerx uses that information to authenticate registered users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Adwerx service and other matters that may be of interest to the user such as special offers. Adwerx also uses the information to provide the products and services requested by the user. 

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Adwerx also logs non-personally- identifiable information such as IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type from users of the Site. This data is used to improve the website services, to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to our users. In the event that we share your email address with a third-party, with the exception of our email service provider, the email will be shared solely in hashed, non-human readable form. IP addresses of those who visit the Site may also be recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

In addition, Adwerx uses pixel tags - tiny graphic images - to tell us what parts of the Website have been visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches users perform on our Site. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format that our users can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we are only sending messages that are of interest to our users. 

Adwerx may also use a Registered User’s email address to send information such as updates, a newsletter or news regarding Adwerx and the Adwerx service. We may send email messages which use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Site. When a customer clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. Adwerx tracks this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email. 

Adwerx may also collect information for market research purposes to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. Adwerx also collects information regarding customer activities on the Site, and on related websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them. 

In cases where you use a mobile device to access our sites or use or applications, we may receive information about the location of your device. 

We use the information that we collect to develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, and other offerings. 

**USE OF COOKIES**  
Adwerx uses cookies to store users’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including: (i) ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information; (ii) to help track usage to help us understand which parts of the Site are most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there; (iii) to make usage of the Site even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications, and (iv) to customize each visitor’s experience and provide greater convenience. 

The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, which will be stored in hashed, non-human readable form. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from Adwerx in order to use most functions on the Site. Please note that Adwerx may allow third party advertisers to set and access their cookies on your computer via their pixel on our website and in email communications for which you have not opted out. Among other things, these third parties may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to enable such third parties to record which ads your browser has loaded and which pages you may have been viewing when the ads were delivered or accessed. The information collected through these functions is subject to the privacy policies of those third parties, not the Adwerx Privacy Policy (however, if the Site uses the Adwerx Platform, its privacy policy (linked above) will apply). 

**DO-NOT-TRACK**  
Our Site does not respond to "do-not-track" settings in users' web browsers at this time. However, there are various ways to opt out of interest-based advertising, such as [TRUSTe’s Ad Choices](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), the Network Advertising Initiative’s [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), the Digital Advertising Alliance’s [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), or you can also visit Google's [Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en) to manage the ads Google serves. 

**LINKS**  
Adwerx may contain links to third party websites. Adwerx is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the Privacy Policy stated on that site. Our Privacy Policy only governs information collected on this Site. 

**CORRECTING/UPDATING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**  
Registered Users may modify any of the personal information contained in their account at any time by logging into the account and accessing Account Info. 

**EMAIL CHOICE / OPT OUT**  
Registered Users who no longer wish to receive promotional messages or updates from Adwerx may choose not to by opting-out. To opt-out, simply log-in to your account, click the “My Account” link, click on “Account Settings” and select the “No” button next to “Receive Email Updates”. All promotional notification emails and Adwerx newsletters also include an opt-out link. Note that users who have opted-out of promotional messages or updates may still receive email messages from Adwerx where necessary to provide a service you have requested or where necessary to inform you of critical information relating to your use of the Site. 

**SECURITY**  
Adwerx Registered User accounts are secured by Registered User-created passwords. Adwerx takes precautions to ensure that account information is kept private. Adwerx uses reasonable measures such as encryption to protect private information that is stored within our database against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, and we restrict access to such private information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Among these measures, when you enter sensitive nformation (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology, which creates an encrypted connection between you and our systems. Once we collect your credit card or debit card information, it is stored encrypted on restricted-access computers that are not directly accessible via the Internet. Please note that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however, and Adwerx cannot guarantee the security of Registered User account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. Registered Users are urged to also take precautions to protect their personal data by changing passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and using a secure web browser. For any additional information about the security measures Adwerx uses on the Site, please contact us at [privacy@adwerx.com](mailto:privacy@adwerx.com). 

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION ADWERX COLLECTS**  
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Adwerx will not disclose personal information to any third party unless it believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Adwerx, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Adwerx Terms and Conditions or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Adwerx reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Adwerx or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. Adwerx takes your privacy very seriously. Adwerx does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared internally within Adwerx. There are also times when Adwerx may make certain personal information about you available to companies that Adwerx has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Adwerx to provide products and services to you on our behalf. For example, these companies may help us process information, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Adwerx’s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to access certain services, offers, and content on the Site, receive customer service, or provide us feedback to improve our products and services. 

**PRIVACY OF CHILDREN**  
This Site and our services are oriented toward a general audience and intended for adults only. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from those under the age of thirteen (13). If you believe that we have inadvertently collected personally identifiable information from a person under thirteen (13), please contact us so that we can investigate and take any necessary remedial measures. 

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**  
Adwerx is a website operated from the United States by a company headquartered in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and governed by applicable U.S. laws and regulations and this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you consent to this transfer and the processing of your data (personal or otherwise) in accordance with U.S. laws and regulations and this Privacy Policy. The applicable laws in the United States regarding the processing of data (personal or otherwise) may be less stringent than the laws in your country. 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
California law permits certain users of our site who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes during the past year. You may make such a request by writing to us at: 

Adwerx, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department - Privacy  
P.O. Box 3848   
Durham, North Carolina 27701 

You may also email us at: [privacy@adwerx.com](mailto:privacy@adwerx.com). 

Please include the full name and contact information for your Adwerx account in your request, and include the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your letter or email. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. 

**CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will indicate at the top of this Privacy Policy when it was last updated. Please review this Privacy Policy every time you access the Site or use our Platform to make sure that you have reviewed the most recent version. 

**CONTACTING THE SITE**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at: [privacy@adwerx.com](mailto:privacy@adwerx.com). Physical inquiries can be sent to the following address: 

Adwerx, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department - Privacy   
P.O. Box 3848  
Durham, North Carolina 27701 

**DISPUTES**  
Any disputes regarding this Privacy Policy are subject to our General Terms and Conditions and will be governed by the laws of the State of North Carolina, applicable to agreements made and performed there. 

© 2018 Adwerx, Inc. All rights reserved.
